<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<android.support.v4.widget.DrawerLayout
        xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
        android:id="@+id/drawer_layout"
        android:background="@color/darkerWhite"

        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="fill_parent">
    <ScrollView android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="fill_parent">
<LinearLayout 
              android:orientation="vertical"
              android:layout_width="match_parent"
              android:layout_height="fill_parent">

    <TextView android:layout_width="fill_parent"
              android:text="Terms of use"
              style="@style/header"
              android:layout_height="wrap_content"/>

    <TextView android:layout_width="fill_parent"
              style="@style/normalText"
              android:text="We are happy to have you as a user of our application and hope we can improve your life with it. Your data will be handled with care. The purpose of this application is not only to make your life better, but also that of other people. The dataset created through the use of this app includes a timestamp, a location, a challenge description, optional motivational messages, and a challenge completed field.\n\nThe pictures used in the proof will not be part of the dataset. This anonymous dataset is used as input to create a 'virtual sports coach' by the partners in the COMMIT P3 / Sensei project (University of Twente, VU University Amsterdam, Sense Observation Systems, Amsterdam University of Applied Sciences, Almende, and Infosys) and will not be available to any other party. You can read more about this project on http://www.commit-nl.nl/projects/sensei-sensor-based-engagement-for-improved-health. You can always ask specific questions to Anne van Rossum: http://www.almende.com/anne-van-rossum.\n\n. This application has been developed by Aster Schultz, Kevin Groen and Dennis Reep. \n\nIt would be great for our research if you would answer the questionnaire in the application correctly. Thanks a lot!"
              android:layout_height="wrap_content"/>

    <Button android:layout_width="fill_parent"
            android:text="I don't agree"
            android:id="@+id/btnDisagree"
            android:layout_marginBottom="1dp"
            android:onClick="onDisagreePressed"
            style="@style/button"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"/>

    <Button android:layout_width="fill_parent"
            android:text="I agree"
            android:id="@+id/btnAgree"
            android:onClick="onAgreePressed"
            style="@style/button"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"/>


</LinearLayout>
        </ScrollView>
    </android.support.v4.widget.DrawerLayout>